So we also have a sidebar over here just like the other tools and we can open it or close
it using this button, this very button. We also can start a new chat or create a new conversation
or create a new page. We can click Discover and we'll be able to go through what's new, you know?
So the weather and Singapore, what else, stories to explore, so some news, you know, some ideas,
some topics, you know, and these are some discovery options that it provides whatever, you know?
We have imagine, so imagine is about inspiring your next image, explore and remix images to make
something of your own, right? So again, it provides you with some ideas, with some images,
with some imagery that you can use and change to pixel art. You can click Try, you know,
and start playing with them. So this imagine thing is also cool. It provides you with images,
so you can get ideas from images, you know, whatever. We also have a library which is about the
images that we've created. So we don't have anything so far, but we need to sign in and we also have
love, blab.